https://www.bushdvd.com/privacy.asp

Member Sign In
PRIVACY POLICY
Effective Date: 12/12/2014
This privacy policy applies to http://www.bushdvd.com owned and operated by NoCash, Inc..
This privacy policy describes how NoCash, Inc. collects and uses the personal information
you provide on our web site: http://www.bushdvd.com.
It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.
If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact
Jason Holt at customerservice@bushdvd.com.
Personal Information
We do NOT collect any personal information about you except your name,
mailing and shipping address, credit card information, and
e-mail address. We collect this information to register our users for an
account and through our "Contact Us" form so we can reply to inquiries
from our customers.
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy.
NoCash Inc. does NOT share, sell, or disseminate any of your personal information with any third parties.
We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to
help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering
customer service. When shipping you an item your address is disclosed to the USPS.
Note: The USPS does not know what is being shipped. These companies are authorized
to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these
services to us.
You do have the right to change any of the requested personal
information. To change any of your personal information go to your
account which can be found under the "Account" tab once you have logged
in.
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.
If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services
contact us at customerservice@bushdvd.com.
We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
We will only disclose your personal
information to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our web site.
If you choose to write a review on this Web site, you should be aware
that any personal information you submit there can be
read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be
used to send you unsolicited messages.
We are not responsible for the
personal information you choose to submit in the
"Write a Review" portion of the web site. To request removal of your personal
information from the "Write a Review" page, contact us at
customerservice@bushdvd.com.
In
some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case
we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
E-Mails
We periodically send out promotional e-mails. We do send confirmational
e-mails, such as shipment confirmations. If you wish to unsubscribe from
receiving promotional emails from us, you may do so by sending an email
to us with 'Unsubscribe' in the subject line or by changing your e-mail preferences on the account page.
Please send this email to
customerservice@bushdvd.com.
Tracking Technologies
Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by NoCash,
affiliates, or analytics. We use Google Analytics. These technologies are used in
analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the
site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may
receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an
individual as well as aggregated basis.
We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember users' settings (e.g.
display preferences), and for authentication. Users can control the use of
cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our
site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.
We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to
manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use
technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this
site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing
activities and interests.
Analytics / Log Files
As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and
store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses,
browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages,
operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information,
which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the
site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic
information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this
automatically-collected data to personal information.
Security
When you submit sensitive information such as credit card, and login
information, your information is transmitted through a state of the art
128-bit SSL encryption. Also, encrypted are pages for our Affiliate
Program where other sensitive information is collected, specifically
social security number and Tax ID number. No method of transmission over the
Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.
Therefore, we
cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security
on our Web site, you can contact us at customerservice@bushdvd.com.
Social Media Features and Widgets
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and
Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on
our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting
on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly.
Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted
directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the
privacy policy of the company providing it.
Links to 3rd Party Sites
Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may
differ from those of NoCash, Inc. If you submit personal information to
any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies.
We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.
Changes in this Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to
this privacy policy, the home page, and other places we deem
appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we
use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
We
reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so
please review it frequently.
If we make material changes to this
policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on
our home page prior to the change becoming effective.
Business Transitions
In the event NoCash, Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a
merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of
its assets, your personal information will likely be
among the assets transferred.
You will be notified either via email or
prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in
ownership or control of your personal information.
Contact Information
Address:
NoCash, Inc.
3148 Midway Dr
San Diego, CA 92110
Phone:
Call Us Toll Free! - 1-877-BUSHDVD (287-4383)
E-mail: customerservice@bushdvd.com
Movie Rental XXX - Rent XXX DVDs Online - Adult Videos for Rent
BushDVD.com offers the largest selection of adult DVDs for rent. Watch Adult DVDs from the convenience of your own home for a low monthly fee, on a Weekly basis (Rent-Per-Title),
or watch your favorite adult movies directly on your computer with Video-On-Demand (VOD). New releases are added daily. There are more than 12,000 adult DVD reviews to help you
choose the movies you want to watch. DVDs are delivered in discreet packaging.
Copyright ©2003-2020, No Cash Inc.
18 U.S.C. § 2257 Record Keeping Requirements Compliance Statement
